Guide to the Ellen McGowan Biddle Shipman papers, 1914-1946.
Shipman, Ellen McGowan Biddle papers, 1914-1946.
- Series IV. Project Files (Plans)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J.C. Brady (Map-case Folder 21-23, 189)
    - Plan of porch steps, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - General construction plan for garden, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Tea house arch details, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Sketch plan for proposed bridge, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Property survey (Blueprint), 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Sketch plan for Kentucky farm, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Plan of roads, paths, and steps, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Construction details for terrace and garden walls, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Contour map of property (Blueprint), 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Proposed bridge over creek - Scheme C (Blueprint), 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - General layout plan of terrace and garden walls, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Plan showing placing of lily boxes, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Construction plan for revised garden walls, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Set of three-bridge plans (Blueprints), 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
    - Revised plan for office porch steps, 1925 (Map-case Folder 23)
  - Mr. And Mrs. J.H. Campbell (Map-case Folder 24-28)
    Location: East Aurora, New York
    - Planting plan for rose garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Design for bath house, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Perennial planting plan for pool garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for service driveway, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Bath house details, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Bath house elevations and section, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Bath house details (x4), 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Perennials planting plan for bowling green, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Sketch of statue, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Bath house elevations (x2), 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Preliminary sketch - stone arch bridge, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Construction plan for pool, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - First and second floor plans - house, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Revised construction plan for bridge, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Bulb planting plan for roof garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Bulb planting plan for bowling green, 1931 (Map-case Folder 24)
    - Details of approach steps to pool, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - General development plan, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Revised first and second floor plans, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Wood balustrade in garden details, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Construction details of walls and steps in upper garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Construction plan for west gate of rose garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Full size detail of swimming pool gutter and coping, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Detail construction plan for steps to tennis court, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for bird garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Tree planting plan, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - General design plan, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Layout plan for garden and service court walls, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Bulb planting plan for perennial garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for pool garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Plan for furniture placement on terraces, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Sketch for flagstone paving, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Tree planting plan for garden areas, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Shrub planting plan for south terrace, 1931 (Map-case Folder 25)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan from bowling green, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Planting plan for tennis court area, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for paved court, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Planting plan for pool in central garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Tree and shrub plan for rose garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Tree planting plan to screen service area, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for entrance court, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for swimming pool area, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for outside bird garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Construction plan for pool, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Sketch of paved court and wall fountain, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - General grading plan, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Plan showing area for boundary planting, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Tree and shrub planting for bowling green, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Construction plan for small pool in rose garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Construction details of walls and steps in upper gardens, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Details of wood seat, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Full size details of pedestal block for fountain, 1931 (Map-case Folder 26)
    - Construction plan for setback on bridge, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Sketch of steps at approach to swimming pool, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Revised plan for bridge over ravine, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Plan for layout of garden areas (x2), 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - First floor of bath house - Number 1 and 2, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Construction plan for swimming pool, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Profile for entrance drive, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - First floor plan of house (Blueprint), 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Plan showing electric outlets at bath houses, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Sketch of location of trees on east terraces, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Suggested treatment of bridge (2 sheets), 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Elevation of antique mantle, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Construction plan of entrance drive, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Plan for laying of flagstone paving, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Suggested planting around pond, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Grading plan for tennis court, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Revised construction plan for road, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Sketches, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Detail of coping for small pool in rose garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 27)
    - Construction plan of concrete paved service court, 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Construction plan for retaining wall around swimming pool, 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan "A" for service driveway, 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Construction plan for planting areas on terrace, 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Construction plan for west gate of rose garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Plan for planting along driveway (FRAGILE), 1930 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Elevation of top of west gate in rose garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Detailed plan of swimming pool (Blueprint), 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - Topographic map of estate (BP), 1931 (Map-case Folder 28)
    - First floor plan for house (Blueprint), 1931 (Map-case Folder 29)
  - Mrs. M.M. Campbell (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Presentation design plan, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
  - Miss Edith Chase (Map-case Folder 29)
    Location: Westbury, Connecticut
    - Shrub and bulb planting plan, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Construction details for service area, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - First floor plan - Dove Cote, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Planting plan - Dove Cote, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Construction plan for pool, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Planting plan around house, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Construction plan for garden, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Sketches, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Revised sketch plan of garden, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Perennial planting plan, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Revised shrub and lower planting plans, 1925 (Map-case Folder 29)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Roy D. Chapin (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Perennial planting plan, 1946 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan, 1946 (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Deatiled Perennial Guide A, B, C, D, 1946 (Map-case Folder 29)
      South Garden Sepia Print
  - Mr. and Mrs. G.L. Callery (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Location: New Castle, Delaware
    - Construction drawing for shrub and perennial border (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Planting plan for perennial border (Map-case Folder 29)
    - Planting plan for shrub beds (Map-case Folder 29)
  - Mr. and Mrs. D. Conoley (Map-case Folder 30)
    Location: Cumberstone, Maryland
    - General design plan for Tulip Hill, 1945 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Planting study by another architect (Blueprint), 1945 (Map-case Folder 30)
  - Mrs. Thurman Chatham (Map-case Folder 30)
    Location: Winston Salem, North Carolina
    - Design plan (Blueprint), 1945 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Diagrammatic planting plan trees and shrubs, 1945 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Sketch of gazebo for summer house, 1945 (Map-case Folder 31)
  - Curry (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 30)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Arthur G. Cummer (Map-case Folder 30)
    Location: Jacksonville, Florida
    - General layout plan for garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Architectural details in garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - General layout plan for retaining wall, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Revised general layout plan, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Sketch of fountain, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - General design plan, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Planting plan for terrace, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Architectural details for niche, pedestal, and seat, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Preliminary design plan, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Planting plan for garden terrace, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Sketch of steps to new garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Architectural details of arch in garden, 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
    - Plot plan (Black and White), 1931 (Map-case Folder 30)
  - Mrs. Henry Corning (Map-case Folder 31)
    - Details in garden (Map-case Folder 31)
  - H.W. Croft (Map-case Folder 31, 33)
    - Detail of arch columns (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 31)
    - Details of bird house and wall (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Grading plan of garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Planting plan for evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Details of garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Shrub planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Wrought iron gate (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Planting plan for garden terraces (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Planting plan for setting of statue (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Planting plan of pool garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Planting plan of flower garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Design plans for gardens (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Details of seat in evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Porch details for garden house (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Garden house details (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Details of garden house - Sheets 3, 4, 7, 9 (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Detail of base for statue (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Foundation plan of garden house (Map-case Folder 33)
    - Details of wrought iron rail at garden house (Map-case Folder 33)
  - Willard M. Clapp (Map-case Folder 31)
    - Construction drawing of wild garden pool (Map-case Folder 31)
  - J. Fenimore Cooper (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Details of doors and windows in house, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Plan of roof at Pergola, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Sketches, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Suggestions for fountain, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Map showing elevations, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Planting plan, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Construction plan of garden, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Construction plan of garden, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Construction plan for bowling green and rose garden, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Construction plan of swimming pool, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Sketch for iron gate, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Plan of terrace, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Planting plan for garden, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Pump house and tool house elevations, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Plan of stone paving at driveway end of terrace, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Planting plan of terrace, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Location of wall, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Planting of long walk, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Design for rose garden, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Sketch plan for swimming pool, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Suggested development of bowling green and rose garden B and D, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Planting plan for bowling green, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Map showing surroundings of house, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
    - Plan showing wall and sizes of rose garden beds, 1916 (Map-case Folder 32)
  - Fine Arts Center (Map-case Folder 34)
    Location: Colorado Springs, Colorado
    - Perennial planting plan for south beds in east court (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Planting plan for perennial border in east court (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Planting plan for south facade (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Planting plan for trees, shrubs, and vines in east court (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Suggestions for further development (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Revised design plan for future development (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Suggestions for present development (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 34)
    - Building plans (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 34)
  - Mrs. Kent Clow (Map-case Folder 35)
    Location: Lake Forest, Illinois
    - Perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Pool location plan (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Sketches showing proposed changes for pool (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Planting plan for small garden (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Suggested revision for garden (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Construction plan for pool (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan along driveway (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Construction plan for dry planted wall (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Terrace plan and details (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Sketch plan of garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 35)
    - Planting plan of center of garden (Map-case Folder 35)
    - General planting plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 35)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Douglas Crooker (Map-case Folder 36)
    Location: Fitchburg, Massachusetts
    - Revised tulip plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Construction plan of pergola (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Revised general design plan (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Construction plan of garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Grading in vicinity of house (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Construction details for pool (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Shrub planting plan for garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Details of pergola steps (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Details of pergola (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 36)
  - Mrs. C.S. Clark (Map-case Folder 36)
    Location: Angola, New York
    - Planting plan for perennial border (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 36)
  - Dr. and Mrs. A.B. Cannon (Map-case Folder 36)
    Location: New Canaan, Connecticut
    - Planting plan for roadside screen (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Preliminary design plan (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Suggested developments of property (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Sketch of entrance (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 36)
    - Plot plan showing trees (Map-case Folder 36)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Henry M. Dodge (Map-case Folder 37)
    Location: Perrysburg, Ohio
    - Topography of porch of estate (White print) (Map-case Folder 37)
    - Design A, B and C for property (White prints) (Map-case Folder 37)
    - Design plan for property (Map-case Folder 37)
    - Construction drawing for entrance drive and court (Map-case Folder 37)
    - Detail of paving for entrance court (Map-case Folder 37)
    - Sketch plan to locate new trees (Map-case Folder 37)
  - Mrs. A.L. Daniels (Map-case Folder 38 and 191)
    - Design plan of flower garden (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Planting plan of garden - Sheet A (Map-case Folder 191)
    - Construction plan of garden (Map-case Folder 191)
    - Suggestion for lattice (Map-case Folder 191)
  - Sarah Duke Memorial, Duke University (Map-case Folder 38-39a)
    Location: Durham, North Carolina
    - Plan for staking out the garden (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Topographic plan of lake area (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Typical section of stone wall, bed, and path (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Topographic map of garden (B (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Topographical map of section garden (White print) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Construction drawing for Pool "A" (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Design plan for Iris Garden (Map-case Folder 38)
    - A Spralawn System for Iris Garden (White print) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Section on center line of Iris Garden (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Section through steps from garden house to pool, etc (Map-case Folder 38)
    - General construction plan (and Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Garden pergola (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Proposed pergola (Blueprint), 1937 (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Proposed pergola - Revised (3 Blueprints), November 1937 (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Prposed pergola - Revised (Blueprint), December 1937 (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Proposed pergola - 3/4 inch scale. Half plan of stairs (Blueprint), November 1937 (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Revised proposed pergola - 3/4 inch scale. Half plan of stairs (Blueprint), December 1937 (Map-case Folder 38)
    - General ground plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Plan for location of box and trees for upper terrace (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Pergola details (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Pergola columns detail (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
      Carolina Steel and Iron Company
    - Pergola erection diagram (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Pergola architecture (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Pergola rafters (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Pergola roof parts (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Unlabelled black print of planting plan for one half of garden (Map-case Folder 38)
    - Slide of slop with elm, hemlock, spruce, and dogwood (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Topographical overview of site including approach drive (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Side of slope with various trees between North Circuit and Main Approach Drive (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Flower gardens and surroundings walks with particular planting listed (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Detail of outer boundary with road (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Overview of gardens (VOID) (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Overview of physical structure of gardens (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Detail of garden section with specific plantings (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Very rough sketch of planting with various ideas for walls and walkways (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Detailed overview of half gardens (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Rough overview of one quarter of gardens (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Rough overview of second quarter of gardens (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Detailed and rough sketch showing one quarter of garden (2 pieces) (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Rough sketch of outer edge with pond and rock ledges (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Sketch with planting plan for outer edge with pond and rock ledges (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Planting plan - One quarter view of gardens (Map-case Folder 39)
    - Plan of location of rock ledges above pond (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Proposed tool house (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Planting plan for pool area (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Planting plan for slope above pond (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Planting plan for perennials at lower terraces (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Perennial planting plan: Section A, B, C, D (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Planting plan for bank south of garden (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Planting plan on bank (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs: Sections A and B, 1938 (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Shrub planting plan for bank behind garden house (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Bulb planting plan: Section A, B, C, D (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Bronze plaque design (3 drawings), 1937 (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Construction plan for stone seat on lower terrace (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Construction plan for pool "B" (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Proposed office building (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - Naturalist planting plan (Map-case Folder 39a)
    - List of plants for Naturalist Planting (Map-case Folder 39a)
  - Joshua Drake (Map-case Folder 40)
    Location: New Hampshire
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 40)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Eugene Dupont (Map-case Folder 40-42 and 192)
    Location: Centerville, Delaware
    - Planting plan for wild garden, 1928 (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Revised sketch design (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Second revised sketch design for garden (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Sketch design for evergreen garden Numbers 1, 2, 3 (Map-case Folder 40)
    - 4 sketches (Map-case Folder 40)
    - General design plan for gardens (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Topography for garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Centerville estate sketch plan (Map-case Folder 42)
      Location: Greenville, Delaware
    - Pool construction plan, 1928 (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan, 1928 (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Bulb planting plan (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Contours of area for proposed site of new dwelling (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Plan for flagging design (Map-case Folder 40)
    - Forged iron hardware for tea house gate wall (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Construction details for door in tea house wall (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Construction details east wall of entrance turnaround, 1928 (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Construction plan for end of wall (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Ramp railing details (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Two sketches of tea house (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Detail of tea house - flagstone paving (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Tea house - Architectural details (multiple drawings) (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Tea house sketch (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Plan of steps, 1928 (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Final revised construction plan of walls for garden (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Details of steps (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Proposed change in terrace plan (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Construction details for garden door (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Construction details east wall of entrance turnaround (Map-case Folder 41)
    - Tree sketch (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Underground sprinkler layout (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (2 plans, VOID) (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Planting plan for evergreen garden (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Bulb planting plan for evergreen garden (x2), 1928 (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Final revised construction plan of walk for garden, 1928 (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Location of electric outlets for tea house, 1928 (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Check plan for measurements and locations, 1928 (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Tea house Sheets 1, 2, 3, 4, 1928 (Map-case Folder 42)
    - East elevation, tea house window trellis (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Preliminary sketch plan for garden (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Original and revised sketches for wrought iron gate (2 sketches), 1931 (Map-case Folder 42)
      Location: Wilmington, Delaware